{
    "id": "fbbfdee56eac4581bc0777bfc23cf0f7",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The country is —————– by factions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "teared",
                "tore",
                "torn"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "58fda96ec9eb487aaae18995f65039e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Once Sydney Smith was asked his name by a servant and found to his dismay that he had —————— his own name.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "forget",
                "forgot",
                "forgotten"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dcd89e8909044e7aa05a6753bf1f5fee"
        },
        {
            "question": "You couldn’t have —————- a better day for a drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "chose",
                "chosen",
                "choosed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec63f4bebf004125ab4b932e9108341b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old beggar was —————— by a mad dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "byte",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0da6c7a1efd54c06a145c1726f718e27"
        },
        {
            "question": "He —————– the book on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "laid",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aec2b72a275c4da5875f193ff42abee3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Walking through the jungle he —————- on a snake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "treaded",
                "trode",
                "troded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7c11a8f9f374814aaae4e3b4e5fc802"
        },
        {
            "question": "He —————— a hasty retreat on the arrival of a policeman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "beat",
                "beated",
                "beaten"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72241e51dcb241c4bf58a0a195957e1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must reap what you have —————–",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sow",
                "sown",
                "sowed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2432420c8905458f9a7dff44be08165d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His voice —————- as he spoke.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shook",
                "shaken",
                "shaked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5023c8dd4e7b4e9fa1e4a96de1b94f9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "His path was not —————– with flowers but he persevered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "strawn",
                "strewn",
                "strewed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0a875c0958cb41bfb669c69b6f9da6c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The explorers were ————— to death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "froze",
                "frozen",
                "freezed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "262bd333ba0442a3ba0a7e8fd22d515d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His voice —————— to a whisper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sink",
                "sank",
                "sunk"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b688fa992274d05a84468860d0a6a7a"
        }
    ]
}